Amit Motiyani

Contact: 9033434147

Email: amotiyani@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/amotiyani2022

Career Aspiration:

I am looking for a long-term opportunity in Sales operations in an IT product-based company for a Local/ International Market. I bring 5 Years of experience and expertise with Sales, Team Leading, Setting Sales Target and Product Demonstration.

Professional Experience:

1. VasyERP (Undertaken by – Reliance Industries)

SALES MANAGER Feb 2019 – Present

Key Responsibilities:

- Leading the team, and guiding them with basics of sales.
- Setting target for each team member and also motivate them to achieve and fulfill that target.
- Setting meetings with the CEO regarding the growth of business and determining key business areas to focus upon.
- Worked with Marketing and Product teams to engage audiences and clients more deeply.
- Also, to fulfill own target along with the team's target in new business development.

2. VasyERP (Formally Known – Croods Consolidates)

SALES EXECUTIVE Feb 2017 – Jan 2019

Key Responsibilities:

- Lead generation through Upwork, Fiverr, Salesforce LinkedIn. Also did cold calling, reference gathering initially to generate leads.
- Meeting with clients PAN India, demonstrating and pitching them with ERP.
- Conducted B2B, B2C and even door to door business operations.
- Closed new business and developed negotiating strategies by coordinating prospects goals and requirements with company objectives and procedures.
- Increasing product sales and generate recurring sales through client communication via CRM, Zoom Meetings, Google Meet, Skype Calls, LinkedIn and other platforms.
- Maintaining relationship and retaining existing clients for newer business.
- Working towards monthly/ annual targets.

3. Collabera Technologies (Vadodara)

Technical Recruiter Feb 2016 – Aug 2016

Key Responsibilities:

- Sourcing potential candidates on niche platforms, like Naukri.com, LinkedIn.
- Making cold calls from the leads generated and closing candidates for suitable positions (includes screening profile, CTC Negotiation).

- Monitoring the process from interviews to final closing of the candidates.
- Maintaining excel sheets of calls made and deals closed.

Education Qualification:

Course	Stream	Board/University	Result
Bachelor of Engineering	EEE (Electrical &	Gujarat Technological	6.5 CGPA
	Electronics	University	(1st Class)
	Engineering)		
H.S.C.	Science	Central Board Of Secondary	58.6%
		Education (CBSE)	
S.S.C.	General	Central Board Of Secondary	79%
		Education (CBSE)	

Workshops Attended:

- "Seven Skills of Highly Effective People" By Himanshu Buch
- "How to sell anything in 3 simple steps" Udemy Course
- "Business-to-Business Sales" LinkedIn Course By Robbie Kellman Baxter

Skills:

- Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel)
- Interpersonal Skills: Leadership & Customer Relations
- Sales & Direct Sales
- Lead Generation, Negotiation, Deal Closure
- Presentation Skills, Debating, Public communication, Anchoring and organizing Events

Personal Information:

Date Of Birth	8 th December, 1992
Gender	Male
Marital status	Unmarried
Languages Known	English, Hindi, Gujarati, Sindhi.
Hobbies	Music, Reading, Travelling
Permanent Address	1406, Nagarwada, Mahudha – 387335
	Dist – Kheda, GJ
Current location	Ahmedabad
Location Preferences	Ahmedabad, Vadodara